module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Where in the body is most of the element iron located?', 
      a: 'Bones', 
      b: 'Blood',
      c: 'Skin',
      d: 'Brain',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where was former President Obama born?', 
      a: 'Illinois', 
      b: 'Michigan',
      c: 'Ohio',
      d: 'Hawaii',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'The flag of Jamaica includes the colors black, green, and _____.', 
      a: 'White', 
      b: 'Orange',
      c: 'Red',
      d: 'Yellow',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Also known as a bomber hat, which hat is a leather cap with large earflaps, a chin strap, and often has a fleece lining?', 
      a: 'Aviator Hat', 
      b: 'Panama Hat',
      c: 'Deerstalker Hat',
      d: 'Boonie Hat',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What Swiss beverage company started in 1783 and sells lemonade, carbonated waters, and ginger ales?', 
      a: 'Stewarts', 
      b: 'Fanta',
      c: 'Schweppes',
      d: 'Vernors',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who voiced Mr. Fox in the 2009 movie "Fantastic Mr. Fox"?', 
      a: 'George Clooney', 
      b: 'Brad Pitt',
      c: 'Adam Sandler',
      d: 'Benedict Cumberbatch',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What TV show began in 1987 and consisted of heavy metal music videos airing on MTV?', 
      a: 'Headbangers Ball', 
      b: 'V-Rock',
      c: 'Heavy Metal Mayhem',
      d: 'Super Metal World',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What late night TV host gained notoriety for previously hosting "The Man Show" and "Win Ben Stein\'s Money"?', 
      a: 'Craig Ferguson', 
      b: 'Conan O\'Brien',
      c: 'Jimmy Kimmel',
      d: 'Seth Myers',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call an atom that has more protons than electrons?', 
      a: 'Molecule', 
      b: 'Isotope',
      c: 'Anion',
      d: 'Cation',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which sport is played using rackets to hit a shuttlecock across a net?', 
      a: 'Racquetball', 
      b: 'Badminton',
      c: 'Squash',
      d: 'Aikido',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};